I will care for all patients equally.
Kebab takeaway on the floor of my room.
Here I am at my new doctor apartment.
Today I'm officially graduating from medical school.
After five years I'm becoming a doctor.
Which sounds mad like, ah.
Cheers.
There is energy to carry on.
I don't know what I was thinking.
Do you know where we collect the gowns?
Up there.
Yeah.
Can you see the going this way?
Oh, yeah.
It's all right.
Just hold this up.
Thank you.
Yeah.
It's almost like swimming caps, so tight but not uncomfortable.
So you put it back in the top there.
A bit too loose?
I think it's fine actually.
I'm not sure if I'm going to actually have time to come here to put
it on.
How would I?
Okay, I can show you.
I'm just going to come and take a look at it.
This should be folded over like that.
It's all flattened out.
Yeah, you can...
How are you feeling?
Good, yeah.
I need to get ready.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna get out of here.
Hey James.
Wait, are you on campus right now?
Yes.
I'm on campus but I'm not even dressed yet.
Yeah, I'm not ready yet.
I'll be there on time, I'll be there on time.
How much for all of this?
No, gown number.
Five pounds or something.
Oh, I bet you.
This is in Maldon.
No, you gotta return it as well.
How much?
Uni is expensive.
Graduating is even more expensive by year.
Turn right onto B3212 We've been actually on the road for like three hours because
my uni is so far from home for me.
It's going to be a little bit chaotic because I also got to move out
of my student house fully and to get our full deposit back me and my
flatmates shared some cleaning duties and I got to hoover the whole house before my
graduation or after.
We just got home and now I'm going to put my makeup on, dress up
and there's no way we have have any time to give the house at all
we're barely gonna make it one time so
is
it oh
my
god
I'm still not wearing
my shoes, oh my god this is too chaotic.
I'm wearing these baba in a bit.
lip swept is for real
I will care for all patients equally.
I will consider the environmental impacts.
The crazy glass.
The incredibly proud.
Thanks, Simon!
You can go that way.
One, two, three!
My son!
Hey!
Congratulations!
I can see my parents taking videos of me because they are doing their best.
They're so cute!
So sweet!
How are you feeling?
I feel amazing.
This is all so surreal.
It feels so good that we can call ourselves doctors.
It's been a long five plus one years.
We literally got into medicine together.
We got each other in and we helped each other throughout.
I value your friendship so much James.
I value yours so much.
Oh my god, maybe I could put like a clip of us when...
The point after.
Yeah.
The glow up.
Yes.
Are we gonna try and throw out cups?
Yeah!
Are you ready?
Yeah, I'm ready!
Woo!
Just done with the graduation and now we're
having some kebab takeaway on the floor of my room because we don't have much
time.
We've got to clean the house quickly and get out of here.
I feel a bit emotional and I don't want to leave.
I'll maybe miss this place, maybe not.
I don't know.
At this point, as the lights ripped the wallpaper off of them, and I made
it worse, trying to patch it up with my mismatched yellow paint, I realised...
It's not looking good Bev.
It's not looking good.
I
hate
the way you talk to me.
and the way you cut your hair.
I hate the way you drive my car.
I hate it when you stare.
I hate your big dog.
What time is it?
It's 1.11.
It's 1.11 and my parents are sleeping in my room because we could not follow
me around.
Of course, that was expected.
And now I'm just hanging out with my friends.
I'm having to stay here tonight because I have nowhere else to go.
So thank you, Noya, for letting me stay.
I can't.
It's nice.
Thank you.
One of the two.
One of the two?
That's basically annoying saying get the hell out of my room.
What did she say?
She's tired.
I'm ready to go to bed.
Alright.
I'm ready to sleep.
Yeah, I mean I just have to change tomorrow for digits.
Good morning.
We are on our way to get some paint to paint over the walls.
A sample with no colour added to it.
Okay perfect.
Thank you so much.
And here is how I saved my £600 deposit with £7 worth of paint.
I got rid of all the blu-tack stains on the walls and ceiling painted over
them and me and mom carefully fixed the damage on the walls and whilst dad
was asleep of
course
Where is it?
They arrived at my new doctor apartment.
Sorry, thank you.
Oh my god, I just met my first flatmate.
After five years of medical school, let's find out where I'm going for my first
job as a doctor.
I'm super anxious honestly.
By the way, my first choice was London and it's the most competitive place in
the UK.
So wish me luck.
Oh wait, it's loading.
I don't want to look.
Shall I look?
I think I should blow.
Oh nooooooo.
What?
But the thing is, this system is all
luck.
It's not about what you get from your exams, it's just pure luck.
And I was unlucky, I guess.
This move feels a bit bittersweet because I've been placed at one of my bottom
choice hospitals in the country.
In a small, quiet town that doesn't really offer much for me.
for me.
So with the new system in the UK, newly graduated doctors like me are assigned
jobs through a random generator.
Unfortunately, I wasn't as lucky as others and got placed in a town far from
my family where I don't know anyone.
Of course, I'm so grateful to have a job and even though it's disappointing, after
working so hard in medical school, my location was decided by a random algorithm.
But I'm choosing to see this as an opportunity to grow and believe everything happens
for a reason or at least I'm trying